Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids: Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：是的，是的，队长。
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:   Aye, aye,
Captain!
孩子们：是啊是啊
队长！
Captain: ♪ Ohh... ♪
队长：♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
孩子们：♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
孩子们：♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
孩子们：♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
孩子们：♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
全部：♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
♪ WhoBob WhatPants ♪
Captain: ♪ WhoBob
WhatPants ♪
队长：♪ WhoBob
什么裤子♪
Man: Patchy the Pirate
presents...
男：海盗帕奇
礼物...
Ahoy, it's a SpongeBob
SquarePants special.
嘿，这是海绵宝宝
方裤特别。
Good morning, Gary.
早上好，加里。
Good morning, Mr. Mailman.
早上好，邮差先生。
'Morning, SpongeBob.
“早上好，海绵宝宝。”
Ah, it  is  a good morning,
isn't it?
啊，这是一个美好的早晨，
不是吗？
Isn't life great, Gary?
生活不是很美好吗，加里？
Oh, what a beautiful day.
噢，多么美好的一天啊。
I have the best friends...
我有最好的朋友...
Ah, stay away!
啊，别走开！
Oh, another SpongeBob nightmare.
哦，又是海绵宝宝的噩梦。
...the best job.
...最好的工作。
He's already 10 seconds late.
他已经迟到了10秒。
I'm docking him
a month's pay for this.
我对接他
为此支付一个月的工资。
And, of course, the bestest pet.
当然，还有最好的宠物。
Ooh...
哦...
I'm sorry!
对不起！
Patrick: Hi, SpongeBob.
帕特里克：嗨，海绵宝宝。
Hey, Patrick, how goes it?
嘿，帕特里克，怎么样？
Well, it  was  going great
until you showed up.
嗯，进展顺利
直到你出现。
What is that?
那是什么？
Oh, just a birthday cake
for my mom.
哦，只是一个生日蛋糕
为了我妈妈。
That I spent all day baking.
我花了一整天的时间烘烤。
Idiot boy.
白痴男孩。
Ooh, that's the first time
somebody's called me that.
哦哦，这是第一次
有人这么叫我。
Wait, I know who will
enjoy my company.
等等，我知道谁会
享受我的陪伴。
Squidward...
章鱼哥...
Don't you  ever  wake me
from my beauty sleep,
do you understand?
你永远别叫醒我
从我的美容觉中，
你明白吗？
Idiot boy.
白痴男孩。
Whoo-ee, it's all done.
呼呼，一切都完成了。
My greatest invention yet.
我迄今为止最伟大的发明。
Sandy, what a neat robot.
桑迪，多么漂亮的机器人啊。
No...
不...
I can explain, you see,
I was up in a tree
我可以解释一下，你看，
我在树上
and I thought it'd be funny
if I gave you a surprise.
我觉得这会很有趣
如果我给你一个惊喜。
Oh, you gave me a surprise,
all right.
哦，你给了我一个惊喜，
好吧。
Look at the surprise I got!
看看我收到的惊喜吧！
Get out of here... idiot boy.
离开这里...白痴男孩。
A place where I'm wanted
whether they like it or not.
一个我被通缉的地方
不管他们喜欢与否。
SpongeBob Work-Pants
reporting for duty, Mr. Krabs.
海绵宝宝工作裤
克拉布斯先生，来上班了。
Hurry up and get in there, boy,
patties need flippin'.
快点进去吧，孩子，
肉饼需要翻转。
No worries, Cap'n.
不用担心，船长。
Oops, eh, all in a day's work.
哎呀，呃，都是一天的工作。
Now back to doing
what I do best.
现在回到做
我最擅长什么。
No way I can mess this up-
Whoa-oh-oh...
我不可能把这件事搞砸-
哇哦哦...
"Well, hello there."
“嗯，你好。”
What the barnacles is going on?!
藤壶这是怎么回事？！
Mr. Krabs, help...
蟹老板，救命啊……
Mr. Krabs, are you OK?
蟹老板，你还好吗？
As long as me money's OK.
只要我有钱就可以了
Mr. Money: Although we've only
known each other a short time
Mr. Money：虽然我们只
认识时间短
I just wanted you to know,
I love you.
我只是想让你知道，
我爱你。
If I were you, I'd get
as far away from me as possible.
如果我是你，我会得到
离我越远越好。
Idiot boy.
白痴男孩。
If Mr. Krabs is calling me
"idiot boy," it must be true.
如果蟹老板打电话给我
“白痴男孩”，这一定是真的。
I know what must be done.
我知道必须做什么。
I've somehow managed
to make everyone mad at me.
我已经设法
让每个人都生我的气。
At least you still like me,
right, Gar'?
至少你还喜欢我
对吧，加尔？
There's a year's supply
of snail food for you.
有一年的供应量
为你准备蜗牛食物。
Good-bye, pineapple.
再见，菠萝。
Good-bye, Squidward.
再见，章鱼哥。
Good-bye, Patrick.
再见，帕特里克。
Good-bye, Sandy.
再见，桑迪。
Good-bye, Bikini Bottom.
再见，比基尼泳裤。
Good-bye, life as I know it.
再见，我所知道的生活。
"Welcome to Bikini Bottom,
population 538."
“欢迎来到比基尼泳裤，
人口538。”
Minus one.
减一。
Idiot boy, idiot boy,
idiot boy...
白痴男孩，白痴男孩，
白痴男孩...
Idiot boy-
白痴男孩——
Whoa!
哇！
Ooh, boy, that's quite a lump.
哦，孩子，那真是个肿块。
Patrick, where's SpongeBob?
帕特里克，海绵宝宝在哪里？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I've been knocking on
his door for three hours
我一直在敲
他的门三个小时
I need his hot sauce
for my milkshake.
我需要他的辣酱
为了我的奶昔。
We ain't got time for that,
hai-yah!
我们没有时间这么做
哈喽！
Gary, where are you, little guy?
加里，你在哪里，小家伙？
Gary, Gary?
加里，加里？
Gary, what happened to you?
加里，你怎么了？
Sandy: A note.
桑迪：一张纸条。
"To whom it may concern.
“敬启者。
"If you've found this letter
“如果你找到这封信
"that means Gary's food bowl
is empty and that it
needs to be refilled.
“这意味着加里的食物碗
是空的并且它
需要重新填充。
"It also means it's been
approximately one year
since I've split town
“这也意味着它已经
大约一年
自从我分开城镇
"and no one's noticed till now.
“而且到目前为止还没有人注意到。
"No one needs to worry,
I won't bother anyone again.
“没有人需要担心，
我不会再打扰任何人了。
"Sincerely, SpongeBob.
“真诚的，海绵宝宝。
A.K.A. Idiot Boy."
又名白痴男孩。”
Man: I could use this.
男：我可以用这个。
Woman: Yeah, I like these here.
女：是的，我喜欢这里的这些。
Man: Mm, this is top quality,
top quality.
男：嗯，这是顶级品质，
一流的品质。
Hello, there, what's going on?
你好，那边，有什么事吗？
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
Oh, we thought you were
taking a dirt nap
哦，我们以为你是
打个小盹
but, uh, we organized your
clothes for you, SpongeBob.
但是，呃，我们组织了你的
给你的衣服，海绵宝宝。
Are you talking to me?
你在跟我说话吗？
Isn't this your name?
这不是你的名字吗？
I don't know, is it?
我不知道，是吗？
You don't know your name?
你不知道你的名字吗？
All I know is I hit my head
on some rocks.
我只知道我撞到了头
在一些岩石上。
Now I can't seem
to remember anything.
现在我似乎看不到
记住任何事情。
Uh, well, then,  .
呃，那么，。
I'll remind you that these
are  not  your clothes.
我会提醒你这些
不是你的衣服。
And your name  isn't  SpongeBob,
it's, uh, mm...
而且你的名字不是海绵宝宝
这是，呃，嗯……
Uh, Cheese-Head Brown-Pants,
, that's it.
呃，奶酪头棕色裤子，
，就是这样。
Cheese-Head, huh?
奶酪头，是吗？
Wait a minute, what's this?
等一下，这是什么？
Man: Bubbles?
男：泡泡？
I wonder what got into them?
我想知道他们身上发生了什么？
Man: We interrupt this program
for an important announcement.
男：我们中断这个程序
发布重要公告。
Bikini Bottom is literally
in a state of total chaos
tonight- ow!
比基尼泳裤实际上是
处于完全混乱的状态
今晚——噢！
Literally.
字面上地。
We go now to News Sea
Chopper Seven, what's up?
我们现在去新闻海
七号机，怎么了？
Not looking too good
up here, Perch.
看起来不太好
在这里，鲈鱼。
The Krusty Krab is just about
to come apart at the hinges.
蟹堡王大约是
在铰链处分开。
Customers are in a rage over not
getting their Krabby Patties.
顾客因不这样做而愤怒
得到他们的蟹肉饼。
Mr. Krabs: Squidward.
蟹老板：章鱼哥。
Where the barnacles
is SpongeBob?
藤壶在哪里
是海绵宝宝吗？
This place is going
down the toilet.
这个地方要去
下厕所。
Patties need flippin'.
馅饼需要翻转。
If I knew, do you think
I'd be standing here
如果我知道，你觉得
我会站在这里
getting yelled at
by a bunch of morons?
被骂
由一群白痴？
Don't talk back to your
superior officer, you...
不要和你顶嘴
上级长官，你...
Sandy: Squidward, Mr. Krabs,
y'all seen SpongeBob?
桑迪：章鱼哥，蟹老板，
你们都看过海绵宝宝吗？
I think we just
went through this.
我想我们只是
经历过这个。
What he means to say is,
"No, we haven't."
他想说的是，
“不，我们没有。”
Well, apparently,
he's left Bikini Bottom
and he ain't coming back.
嗯，显然，
他离开了比基尼泳裤
他不会回来了。
Let me see that.
让我看看。
"To whom it may concern..."
“敬启者...”
"Akkah, Idiot Boy."
“阿卡，白痴男孩。”
Idiot Boy?!
白痴男孩？！
It  is  SpongeBob.
它是海绵宝宝。
What am I gonna do
without me fry cook?
我要做什么
没有我炒菜吗？
What am I gonna do
without my best friend?
我要做什么
没有我最好的朋友？
I should never have been
mean to you.
我本来就不应该
对你来说意味着。
I should've never
kicked you out of my house.
我不应该
把你赶出了我的房子。
if I'd known that was the last
time I'd ever see SpongeBob
如果我知道那是最后一次
我什么时候能看到海绵宝宝
I would've slammed the door
in his face even harder.
我会关上门
在他脸上更加难受。
All right, group meeting.
好的，小组会议。
Everybody out.
大家都出去吧。
The Krusty Krab's closed
until further notice.
蟹堡王关门了
直至另行通知。
Now how do you propose we find
me money-makin' employee?
现在你建议我们如何找到
我是赚钱的员工吗？
Whoo, I live in a dump.
哇，我住在垃圾场。
Hey, watch where
you're steppin'.
嘿，看哪里
你正在迈步。
Sorry, sir, I was just-
抱歉，先生，我只是——
I know what you was doing,
you was doing
我知道你在做什么
你在做什么
the ol' "bump into the sucker
and reach into his pockets
and take his change" routine.
ol'“撞到吸盘上
然后把手伸进口袋
并接受他的改变”例行公事。
Well, it ain't gonna
work  this  time.
嗯，这不会
这次工作。
You want money,
get a job, you deadbeat.
你想要钱，
找份工作吧，你这个赖账者。
I'm a jobless deadbeat?
我是一个无业游民吗？
What a sad existence
I don't remember I lead.
多么可悲的存在
我不记得我是领导者。
Ooh, seems like
I'm running on empty.
哦哦，好像
我空空地跑。
Aw, I guess if I want to
fill the hole in my gut
噢，我想如果我愿意的话
填补我肠道中的空洞
I'll need to
fill a job somewhere.
我需要
在某处填补一份工作。
"Help wanted"?
“把招工广告”？
Well, Mr. Brown-Pants,
you seem to have left
this entire application blank.
嗯，棕色裤子先生，
你好像已经离开了
整个申请表都是空白的。
Well, do you have
any special skills?
嗯，你有吗
有什么特殊技能吗？
Special skills?
特殊技能？
Oh, I can do this...
哦，我可以做到这一点...
What do you think you're doing?
你认为你在做什么？
Sorry, sir, but we run
a respectable business here.
对不起，先生，但我们跑了
这里是一家受人尊敬的企业。
OK, I guess they don't want you
blowing bubbles
好吧，我猜他们不想要你
吹泡泡
unless it directly relates
to the job at hand.
除非直接相关
到手头的工作。
Thanks for the job, boss,
you won't be disappointed.
感谢老板的工作，
你不会失望的。
That's real sweet, Brown-Pants,
but I don't hear that
hammer pounding.
真的很可爱，棕色裤子，
但我没听到
锤子敲击。
Then this must be
music to your ears.
那么这一定是
音乐传到你的耳朵里。
You aren't doing that on my
building site, you're fired.
你没有对我这样做
建筑工地，你被解雇了。
I do  not  understand this.
我不明白这一点。
What is wrong with this city?
这座城市出了什么问题？
Maybe it's not the city,
maybe it's me.
或许这不是一座城市
也许是我。
Hey, mister, look at me,
mister, look at me!
嘿，先生，看着我，
先生，看着我！
Is there something
wrong with me?
有什么东西吗
我错了吗？
Sandy: Listen up, y'all.
桑迪：你们听着。
I've got a plan
to bring back SpongeBob.
我有一个计划
把海绵宝宝带回来。
You do?
你做？
Yup, and it involves this.
是的，它涉及到这一点。
It'll track any sponge
within a 50-mile radius.
它会追踪任何海绵
50 英里半径内。
Oh, you're saying this thing
can actually  find  SpongeBob?
哦，你说的是这个
真的能找到海绵宝宝吗？
You got it, Squid-cakes.
你明白了，鱿鱼饼。
But it's gonna take
all of us to find-
但这需要
我们所有人都要找到——
Oops, I dropped it.
哎呀，我把它掉了。
Mr. Squidward!
章鱼哥先生！
This device was me
last chance to get this place
back into ship-shape.
这个设备就是我
获得这个地方的最后机会
恢复成船形。
And since you destroyed it, I'm
ordering  you  to find SpongeBob.
自从你毁了它以来，我
命令你找到海绵宝宝。
I wouldn't seek out that twit
for all the leotards in the sea.
我不会去找那个傻瓜
对于海里所有的紧身衣。
If you don't find him,
you'll be out of a job forever.
如果你找不到他
你将永远失业。
Ha, is that your version
of a threat?
哈，是你的版本吗
威胁？
Oh, Squidward, don't forget
your retirement gift.
哦，章鱼哥，别忘了
您的退休礼物。
Squidward: Mr. Krabs,
I am not interested in any-
章鱼哥：蟹老板先生，
我对任何事情都不感兴趣——
That'll complete my collection.
这将完成我的收藏。
Oh, thank you, thank you,
thank you, Mr. Krabs.
哦，谢谢你，谢谢你，
谢谢你，蟹老板。
Not so fast.
没那么快。
Bring back me number-one
fry cook first.
把我带回第一
先炒煮。
Real drag, isn't it?
真正的阻力，不是吗？
Having to stand around a fire
for warmth every night.
必须站在火边
为了每一个夜晚的温暖。
Yeah.
是的。
Hey, not for us.
嘿，不适合我们。
We're just waiting in line
for a new video game.
我们只是在排队等候
一个新的视频游戏。
I guess I am just
a jobless deadbeat.
我想我只是
一个无业游民
You guys mind if I bubble?
你们介意我冒泡泡吗？
You can't do that here.
你不能在这里这样做。
But bubbles will steady
the old nerves, watch.
但泡沫将会稳定下来
老神经，看吧。
Ah, see, feeling better already.
啊，看吧，感觉好多了。
Don't look.
别看。
Do you have any-
你有没有——
I think we've made our point
with the snapping.
我想我们已经表达了我们的观点
随着啪的一声。
As I was saying, do you have
any idea who we are?
正如我所说，你有
知道我们是谁吗？
Um, hold on, wait-wait,
don't stop me, um-
嗯，等等，等等，
别阻止我，嗯-
Don't answer.
不要回答。
I'll show you.
我会告诉你。
We call us
the Bubble-Poppin' Boys.
我们打电话给我们
泡泡男孩。
And Article One of our charter
prohibits bubble blowing
on our turf.
以及我们章程的第一条
禁止吹泡泡
在我们的地盘上。
You see why we don't
allow bubbles in our city?
你知道为什么我们不这样做
允许我们的城市出现泡沫吗？
Fortunately, we have ways
of dealing with careless
bubble-blowers like you.
幸运的是，我们有办法
处理粗心的
像你这样吹泡泡的人
Let's  rough  him up, boys.
孩子们，让我们粗暴地对待他吧。
Where'd he go?
他去哪儿了？
After him.
在他之后。
Ah, I'll be making
this getaway in comfort.
啊，我会做
这次舒适的度假。
Do you realize what you've done?
你意识到你做了什么吗？
No...
不...
You have freed this city.
你解放了这座城市。
Citizens of New Kelp,
come out of the shadows
新海带的公民们，
走出阴影
'cause Cheese-Boy kicked
the Bubble-Poppin' gang
right out of town.
因为奶酪男孩踢了
泡泡帮
就在城外。
Thank you, Cheese-Boy.
谢谢你，奶酪男孩。
What an amazing gift
Cheese-Boy has given us.
多么奇妙的礼物啊
奶酪男孩给了我们。
Actually, it's Cheese-Head.
事实上，它是奶酪头。
Well, Cheese-Head
好吧，奶酪头
this is an historic day
for New Kelp City.
这是历史性的一天
为新海带城。
You have rid this city
of the Bubble-Poppin' Boys.
你已经摆脱了这座城市
泡泡男孩的成员。
And restored bubble-blowing
to the streets.
并恢复吹泡泡
到街上。
Something I wasn't able
to do for 20 years as mayor.
一些我无法做到的事情
当了20年市长。
For this, I appoint you
mayor of New Kelp City.
为此，我任命你
新海带市市长。
Long live Mayor Cheese-Head.
奶酪头市长万岁。
Sandy: SpongeBob...
桑迪：海绵宝宝……
SpongeBob...
海绵宝宝...
Maybe someone at that truck stop
has seen our porous
little buddy.
也许那个卡车停靠站有人
看到了我们的多孔
小伙伴。
Patrick: SpongeBob!
帕特里克：海绵宝宝！
There he is, guys.
他就在那里，伙计们。
Huh?
啊？
Oh, I knew I'd find you, buddy.
哦，我就知道我会找到你，伙计。
Look at you, you haven't
changed a bit.
看看你，你还没有
改变了一点。
Let's go home and eat
a gallon of sea-nut butter.
我们回家吃饭吧
一加仑海坚果酱。
That's not SpongeBob, Patrick.
那不是海绵宝宝，帕特里克。
There's SpongeBob.
有海绵宝宝。
I'll get you out of
this cage, buddy.
我会把你救出来
这个笼子，伙计。
You're safe now in my arms.
你现在在我怀里很安全。
Huh, well, where'd you go now?
嗯，那么，你现在去哪儿了？
Uh, Pat?
呃，帕特？
All the ink came off
on your belly.
所有墨水都脱落了
在你的肚子上。
Oh.
哦。
Now let's see what that
little critter's up to.
现在让我们看看那是什么
小动物在做什么。
"New Mayor of-"
“新任市长——”
SpongeBob's mayor of
New Kelp City.
海绵宝宝的市长
新海带城。
Citizens of New Kelp City.
新海带市的市民。
I don't know much about politics
or balanced budgets
我对政治了解不多
或平衡预算
or how to be a "leader."
或者如何成为“领导者”。
I'm not exactly sure
what a "mayor" "is."
我不太确定
“市长”是什么？
But I do know this, while I am
wearing the mayor's hat
但我确实知道这一点
戴着市长的帽子
it will always be safe to blow
bubbles on the streets
of New Kelp
吹起来总是安全的
街道上的泡泡
新海带
or my name isn't
Cheese-Head Brown-Pants.
或者我的名字不是
奶酪头棕色裤子。
Cheese-Head Brown-Pants?
奶酪头棕色裤子？
New Kelp City has
Brown-Pants mania.
新海带城有
棕色裤子狂热。
Sandy: Hang on a minute.
桑迪：等一下。
I don't mean to put a damper
on the mood here
我并不是有意要放一个阻尼器
关于这里的心情
but Bikini Bottom
needs you back, SpongeBob.
但比基尼下装
需要你回来，海绵宝宝。
What's that?
那是什么？
Well, I'm sorry
I yelled at you, buddy.
嗯，对不起
我对你大喊大叫，伙计。
Oh, this is a surprise.
哦，这真是一个惊喜。
Surprised I found you?
很惊讶我发现了你？
No, surprised at seeing
a talking weasel.
不，看到后很惊讶
一只会说话的黄鼠狼
Don't pretend you don't
remember me, SpongeBob.
不要假装你不这样做
请记住我，海绵宝宝。
Sorry... Sandy.
抱歉...桑迪。
But I'd probably remember
an underwater, talking weasel.
但我可能会记得
一只在水下会说话的黄鼠狼。
You may not remember the weasel
你可能不记得黄鼠狼
but you haven't forgotten
your best friend, have you?
但你没有忘记
你最好的朋友，是吗？
I have no idea
how that got there.
我不知道
那是怎么到那里的。
All I remember is hitting
my head, blowing some bubbles
and now, poof, I'm mayor.
我只记得击打
我的头，吹着泡泡
现在，噗，我是市长了。
You must've lost your memory
when you hit your head.
你一定是失去了记忆
当你撞到你的头时。
You'll just have to come back
with us to Bikini Bottom.
你只需要回来
和我们一起去比基尼堡。
The familiar surroundings will
bring your memory right back.
熟悉的环境将
立即恢复你的记忆。
Uh, sorry, weasel girl,
I can't leave.
呃，对不起，黄鼠狼女孩，
我不能离开。
These people need my leadership.
这些人需要我的领导。
In fact, I'm late for a meeting.
事实上，我开会迟到了。
Sandy: SpongeBob, wait!
桑迪：海绵宝宝，等等！
Don't just stand there, get in.
别只是站在那里，进去吧。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Decorative egg, here I come.
装饰蛋，我来了。
here it is.
这里是。
You must recognize this place.
你一定认得这个地方。
Nope.
没有。
Don't recognize the Krusty Krab?
不认识蟹堡王？
Stop your kidding, boy.
别开玩笑了，孩子。
And start frying up
them patties.
他们肉饼。
I was a fry cook before?
我以前是炒菜的吗？
Aye, the best in the business.
是的，业内最好的。
Now get flippin'.
现在开始吧。
Look, guys,
as much as I'd love to
瞧，伙计们，
尽我所能
toil the days away
flipping burgers
辛苦劳作的日子
翻转汉堡
I think I'll just
go back to my modest job
as mayor of a major city.
我想我只会
回到我平凡的工作
作为一个大城市的市长。
Whoo-hoo-hoo,
SpongeBob's leaving for real
this time.
呼呼呼，
海绵宝宝真的要离开了
这次。
Mr. Krabs, I brought back
your number-one fry cook.
蟹老板，我带回来了
你的第一名炒菜厨师。
You  gotta pay up.
你得还钱。
All right, Mr. Squidward,
a deal's a deal.
好吧，章鱼哥先生，
协议就是协议。
Here's your fancy egg.
这是你的精美鸡蛋。
Oh, it's beautiful.
哦，很漂亮。
No...
不...
You OK, SpongeBob?
你还好吗，海绵宝宝？
Hey, I remember this place.
嘿，我记得这个地方。
SpongeBob's back.
海绵宝宝回来了。
We're really sorry
we ran you out of town, boy.
我们真的很抱歉
我们把你赶出了城，孩子。
But we're glad you're back.
但我们很高兴你回来了。
I'd really love to stay,
but the people of New Kelp City
need their mayor.
我真的很想留下来
但新海带城的人们
需要他们的市长。
Good-bye, everyone.
再见，大家。
Huh?
啊？
Oh, not again.
哦，不会了。
He's leaving... Again.
他要离开……再一次。
Man on TV: Stop what
you're doing and  don't
go out that door.
电视里的人：停下来
你正在做和没有做
走出那扇门。
This is a K-N-K-C
special report.
这是一个 K-N-K-C
特别报告。
Panic in the streets
of New Kelp City
街头一片恐慌
新海带城
as rampant bubbles bring
visibility down to zero.
正如猖獗的泡沫带来的
能见度降至零。
The angry citizens here blame
the apocalyptic scene
这里愤怒的市民指责
世界末日的场景
on Mayor Cheese-Head Brown-Pants
and his newly-enacted
bubble policy.
市长奶酪头棕色裤子
以及他新制定的
泡沫政策。
If I ever see
Mayor Brown-Pants again
如果我见过
又是棕裤市长
I'm gonna grab his little,
yellow head
我要抓住他的小
黄头
and literally rip his-
并从字面上撕裂他的-
Where's SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝在哪里？
Who wants to be a dumb
old mayor when you're
the best fry cook in town?
谁愿意当个傻子
老市长当你
城里最好的炒菜厨师？
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy...
哦，男孩，哦，男孩，哦，男孩……
Krabby Patty.
克拉比·帕蒂。
SpongeBob, another masterpiece.
海绵宝宝，又一杰作。
It's great to have you
back, Spongey.
很高兴有你
回来吧，海绵。
Looks like I'm back in
Bikini Bottom forever.
看来我又回来了
永远的比基尼泳裤。